

jessicajzhong@gmail.com

650-255-2187



in linkedin.com/in/jessicazhong



jessicazhong.design

# SUMMARY

A Product Designer with a business acumen focused on people. I am committed to creating better user-focused experiences through a deep understanding of people by identifying real-life problems and crafting thoughtful solutions grounded by research

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BLOC.IO**

**UX/UI** Design Apprenticeship Nov 2018 - June 2019

# UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA **SAN DIEGO**

**B.S Management Science** 

# **SKILLS**

### **DESIGN**

**UX** Design Visual Design **User Research Usability Testing Brand Design & Identity Information Architecture** Wireframing **Prototyping** Sketching

#### **DESIGN TOOLS**

Sketch

**Figma** 

UsabilityHub

**InVision** 

**Affinity Designer** 

Draw.io

Maze

#### **WEB DEVELOPMENT**

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript (basic)

# **RECENT PROJECTS**

### **TRAVELPAK** | WEB & MOBILE APPLICATION

jessicazhong.design/project2.html

- A travel planning web and mobile application designed to help group travelers plan, manage and organize trips, making group travel planning easier than ever
- Utilized Sketch, InVision, lofi wireframes, hi-mockups, in-person usability testing, visual and interation design with branding and content development

#### **HEALTHPOINT** | MOBILE APPLICATION

jessicazhong.design/project1.html

- A cloud-based mobile application that provides health enthusiasts an improved way to collect and store data, with the ability to analyze, connect and organize in the palm of their hand
- Utilized Sketch, Figma, Draw.io to create user flows, wireframes, mockups, usability testing and branding work

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Freelance UX/Product Designer

June 2019 - current

- Providing UX consultation and designs for a client's mobile application and another client's e-commerce website
- Strategizing and collaborating with clients by producing lofi wireframes, sitemap, and hi-fi mockups
- Developing brand design, visual design and style guide

# **JOBVITE** | HR GENERALIST

Apr 2017 - Jan 2019

- Spearheaded company's first Wellness Initiative, resulting in a 45% participation rate for the first year, across all programs for a company of 195 employees
- Implemented a candidate-focused and new hire survey into Jobvite's platform to analyze tangible data regarding the health of Jobvite's brand and candidate experience